Reine.
Good morning, Reine.
Hmm?
Was I actually just—
Yes, you fell asleep.
Though only for about five minutes.
Reine?
Reine's laughing.
This is the first time I've heard
Analyst Murasame laugh.
I see.
I did, huh?
Well then, I've lost.
U-Um, what's gotten into you?
You have my thanks.
It's been a long time
since I fell into a pleasant sleep.
Your shoulder must have been quite comfortable.
Shido!
There's a fluctuation in Reine's
affection and mental state!
Do it now!
Reine.
Hmm? Why are you looking serious?
Earlier...
you mentioned having someone you loved,
but could I be that man?
I know I'll never be a replacement for them.
But would you let me love you in
my own way that's different from them?
Reine.
Shin, I...
We did it!
Commander!
These numbers are abnormal!
Huh?
Her spirit power isn't flowing into me?!
I see. You've seen the future, huh?
What are you so surprised for?
It's possible to share memories
once a pass is formed.
It's not your first time
experiencing it, right?
Now I've solved the mystery behind today.
No, I think I might have vaguely sensed it,
but I imagine I didn't want to understand it.
Because I was very happy
when you invited me on a date.
I really did have fun.
So much so that I was able to forget
my harsh past for a short time.
Though all dreams must come to an end.
Isn't that right,
Shido?
Shido! It's DEM!
Huh?!
It would seem history's been rewritten.
Would you return to Fraxinus with me, Reine?
After we defeat DEM,
you could live together with me
and all the other Spirits.
I'm sure every day would be fun.
Yes, that's a very attractive offer.
I'm sure I would've taken it up without
a second thought if I hadn't met Shin.
Then—!
But I can't.
Because I did meet Shin.
It's a genuine fact that
I love all the Spirits too,
but I'm willing to throw away everything
if it means reuniting with Shin.
Kurumi?!
Why?!
"Why?" is quite the greeting.
Especially when I came running to your aid.
Kurumi, huh?
I'm glad you came.
Having you here makes things quick.
My, my, you're as arrogant
and intolerable as ever,
Spirit of Origin.
I can't believe I let you completely fool me.
I never even imagined
my bitter enemy would be so close by.
Either way,
this means the remaining two Sephirah
possessed by you and Westcott
have been gathered here.
That's enough to awaken Shin.
Well now, I wonder
if it will go that easily for you?
I'm taking them back, Kurumi.
Both the Sephirah inside you,
and my other half.
Hah! I refuse to let you!
Come to me, Kurumi.
Kurumi!
I've been waiting for this moment!
Zaphkiel!
Kurumi?
Mio.
It's been a long time since you've
seen me in this form.
No, you've already met me in this form
in a future I don't know of, haven't you?
That's a bit complicated.
You don't have Kurumi's Sephirah?
That girl must have done something.
Leave it to my dear best friend.
Shin?
Are these?!
DEM warships approaching!
They'll be entering firing range at any moment!
Shido, we're retrieving you.
Then we're taking a moment to regroup.
Shin, what's the matter?
Shin?
He was taken back by Fraxinus?
I suppose that might be
the safest place for him right now.
It wouldn't be very nice if those crude wizards
and automatons destroyed this scenery.
Ein Sof Ohr!
Shido!
-Shido!
-Darling!
-Boy!
-Master!
Tohka, everyone...
Are you all right?
Did Mio do anything to you?
No, though I was a little confused from
Mio's memories flooding into me all at once.
I'm fine now.
Commander, that's...
So that's Ein Sof Ohr?
The Spirit of Origin's Angel...
I had heard about it,
but I didn't realize it was that powerful.
Let's fall back while DEM
is keeping Mio occupied.
We can't!
Hmm?
I can't run away yet!
What are you saying?!
Our operation has failed.
We need to withdraw and think of our next move.
Someone is seeking communication with us.
What shall I do, Kotori?
All right, put them through.
Shido! Look!
Huh? The school?
What's going on?
Captain, Mike, and Milly?
Yuzuru, that's...!
Astonishment. That's our classroom.
What is this?
Is it a terrorist?!
What's going on?!
It's exactly as you see, members of Ratatoskr.
Westcott!
It's good to do things
like this now and then, isn't it?
Now that Deus has manifested,
I'd like to finish up our business
as quickly as possible.
Are you threatening us?!
There's no deal to be had here though.
If we hand the Sephirah over to you,
you'll just overwrite the entire world.
That would defeat the entire point.
Then I'll simply murder those girls
as brutally as possible.
If even one Spirit inverts,
then that's enough for me.
What's going on?!
Design-wise, these aren't
heroes of justice, are they?
They're more like minions of evil, if anything.
That's so lame.
Help!
I wanted to bury my face in a woman's
thighs at least once before I died!
E-Everyone, please hurry up and run!
We're already surrounded, though!
Huh?
Are you okay, Ai, Mai, Mii?
Also, Tonomachi and Tama.
Tohka?!
Yatogami?!
That's so lame!
Everyone, stick together in one spot!
O-Origami?!
Good!
Hmm, it looks like everyone made it in time.
Though I was worried
about long-distance transit.
Oh, god, will we be able to cover
all this up, even with Ratatoskr's power?
My stomach is already upset at the thought.
Hmm...
Still, we weathered that, Isaac Westcott!
That truly was a brilliant showing.
Though one always keeps
their trump card in reserve.
What was that?
A DEM warship has rammed Fraxinus.
It appears to be synchronizing
its territory and docking with ours.
Goetia! Ellen Mathers?!
It's delusional to think
you're safe inside your warship.
At least it is when facing me!
One always keeps their trump card in reserve.
That certainly is a nice phrase,
coming from a brutish president.
Mana!
Shido, that's reckless!
My, my, the siblings all together.
Would you let me join in too?
Nibeelcole!
Westcott!
What's happening to the DEM warships?
They're under attack from Ein Sof Ohr!
Several ships have suffered major damage
and their formation is in disarray!
He's targeting Shido while the warships
are drawing Mio Takamiya's attention.
I can't believe he's willing
to use entire warships as bait...
That's a bold move.
This is no time to be impressed.
I'm leaving the bridge to you, Kannazuki.
Yes, ma'am!
Brother!
Here's some nostalgic faces all together.
It feels like I've gone back into the past.
Yeah, that's true.
Neither you nor Ellen have moved on since then.
Though normally one would show
at least some growth after all this time.
Honestly, I would love to
reminisce about old times,
but unfortunately I'm short on time.
I'll be finishing this
before your Spirits return.
Tsk!
If you're talking about
siblings being together,
then aren't you forgetting one of us?
Kotori!
There's no other choice.
Mukuro needs to maintain the portals
so everyone can return,
and Nia doesn't have the power left to fight.
That means I'm the only one left.
But still...
Don't worry.
I can wield my power for a bit before getting
overwhelmed by my destructive impulse.
It would be a bad joke if I couldn't do
anything during an emergency like this.
Kotori...
Sandalphon!
Wolftail!
Camael!
Here we come, Isaac Westcott!
We'll show you the combined might
of us three siblings!
Right, Kotori?
Are we really three siblings?
This isn't the time for nitpicking details.
Amusing.
Try and fight your fate, humans.
We'll soon arrive at the battlefield, Elliot.
Deus...
Mio, huh?
It's the Spirit we all summoned
thirty years ago.
In order to get revenge on mankind.
Good grief, I fell for quite the evil woman.
Though if Deus is going to fight the other
Spirits, then I can't leave her alone.
Which should we protect?
That's obvious. Both.
Both?
Do you think that's even possible?
It would be impossible on my own.
But that boy,
Shido Itsuka should be
thinking the same thing I am.
So you're going then, Elliot?
Yeah.
Karen, I'm counting on you to prepare Wodan.
Do you find it hard to believe
that the man who betrayed his allies
in order to protect a Spirit
would risk his life to fulfill that duty?
I've followed you this far
precisely because you're like that.
Please, Karen.
Sir Woodman, we're awaiting your orders.
This is...
This response is...
Brother!
Shido!
Now, this is the end.
Dammit! It can't end here!
Now then, it's finally time
to repay that favor,
Episode 10
A Battlefield That Shouldn't Be Possible
Shido.
Episode 11: "A Fleeting Paradise"
Everyone has a summer they'll never forget.
Next time is Episode 11: A Fleeting Paradise.
"If only I could regain that happiness."
Is it really a sin to wish for that?